[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "You___tired.",
        "options": ["are", "is", "am"],
        "answer": "are"
    },

    {
        "id": 2,
        "question":"I ___ a teacher.",
        "options": ["am", "is", "are"],
        "answer": "am"

    },
    
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "She ___ very happy." ,
        "options": ["am", "is", "are"],
        "answer": "is"
    },
    
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "They ___ students." ,
        "options": ["am", "is", "are"],
        "answer": "are"
    },
    
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "He ___ my  brother.",
        "options": ["am", "is", "are"],
        "answer": "is"
    },
    
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "We ___ ready for the test.",
        "options": ["am", "is", "are"],
        "answer": "are"
    },
    
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "You ___ my best friend.",
        "options": ["am", "is", "are"],
        "answer": "are"
    },
    
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "It ___ a nice day.",
        "options": ["am", "is", "are"],
        "answer": "is"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "I ___ at home now.",
        "options": ["am", "is", "are"],
        "answer": "am"
    },
    
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "They ___ in the classrom.",
        "options": ["am", "is", "are"],
        "answer": "are"
    },
    
    {
        "id": 11,
        "question": "My mother ___ a nurse.",
        "options": ["am", "is", "are"],
        "answer": "is"
    }
    
]